{"data":{"createNewExamAttempt":{"attempt":{"id":"71b53763-6ad5-409e-8b10-bb5e1e2f8e66"},"exam":{"id":"b2ea38b4-757b-4de1-ab44-0c3a574c3748","title":"AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam","duration":5400,"totalQuestions":65,"questions":[{"id":"w53824dy-uk0y-a0r6-b6eu-8t2xzl3155or","domain":"tech","question":"Yourself and a colleague both want to create a bucket called \"myawsomebucket\" to store your study notes - will you both be able to do this?","explanation":"As S3 bucket names are global, they need to be globally unique meaning you and your colleague cannot have two buckets with the same name, no matter the circumstances","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/Welcome.html","title":"What Is Amazon S3?"}],"answers":[{"id":"3de7dd4f2d662d5eecc35fa4eadaa8c8","text":"Yes, as long as you are using different AWS Regions","correct":false},{"id":"bafd7322c6e97d25b6299b5d6fe8920b","text":"No","correct":true},{"id":"e90d556314ed67ac2dcf70aa2bd7fefd","text":"Yes, as long as you are using different AWS Accounts","correct":false},{"id":"93cba07454f06a4a960172bbd6e2a435","text":"Yes","correct":false}]},{"id":"16rz9iw6-s5av-nrg1-1gja-89cbrnwj8uco","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are storage services?","explanation":"VPC is a Networking service, and RDS is a Database service, leaving S3 and Elastic File System as the storage services","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/efs/","title":"About EFS"}],"answers":[{"id":"94a6c127c422f3501ac2fd0084ebbd25","text":"AWS VPC","correct":false},{"id":"6e11595bc7ccdbf672fefaababf72939","text":"AWS RDS","correct":false},{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":true},{"id":"1dbd7e466350bb810a3ea48be7668773","text":"AWS Elastic File System","correct":true}]},{"id":"338d1783-ff92-46f0-b582-c4bb314efcff","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is the collection of tools used for developing and managing applications on AWS?","explanation":"Software Development Kits, or SDKs, provide everything you need to develop and manage applications in AWS, including the programming language of your choice.","links":[{"url":"https://d0.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws-overview.pdf","title":"Overview of Amazon Web Services"}],"answers":[{"id":"0654ac3bb453dcb388c05bee59caa0be","text":"Software Development Kits","correct":true},{"id":"41942dbedbefdea8b52c300f0dc777d0","text":"Programming Languages","correct":false},{"id":"a3b73fb1194d31eec199838e4fc4c08a","text":"AWS Management Console","correct":false},{"id":"4b77a7b9a57e83d2c4b01e16f3234143","text":"Command Line Interface","correct":false}]},{"id":"3lwo2qi6-7yzt-o86p-u1vg-vxwsbedkzwt0","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are components of the Security Pillar of the AWS Well-Architected Framework?","explanation":"IAM, Detective Controls and Infrastructure Protection are key parts of the Security Pillar of the Well Archtiected Framwork. IAM - ensuring that only authorized and authenticated users are able to access your resources. Detective Controls to identify a potential security threat or incident. Infrastructure Protection covers the control methodologies, such as defense in depth, necessary to meet best practices and organizational or regulatory obligations.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/architecture/well-architected/","title":"The Well-Architected FRamework"}],"answers":[{"id":"96c4db3cd9b4be5b89474dff6d0fe9b1","text":"Infrastructure protection","correct":true},{"id":"41dff7155cc7aeb11c06434f6a450bb3","text":"IAM","correct":true},{"id":"d5552e0564007d93ff5937a9cb3bc491","text":"Customer Service","correct":false},{"id":"a571cb3f6a39b87e03d60bce4e086f6c","text":"Technical Account Management","correct":false},{"id":"b9237ed805ea2fe23003f7e73fc1f7d4","text":"Detective Controls","correct":true}]},{"id":"ef918c09-219a-45b3-b1cc-f5b02cdbfc1d","domain":"concepts","question":"What type of placement group should you use to spread Amazon EC2 instances across logical partitions so that they don’t share the same underlying hardware?","explanation":"With a partition placement group, EC2 instances are placed into logical segments called partitions, each of which has its own set of racks to supply its network and power source. This level of isolation is designed to prevent the impact of hardware failure within your application.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/placement-groups.html","title":"Placement Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"249694a485fc5d3289c38986b4f8e887","text":"Cluster","correct":false},{"id":"66f9c6c5b672ee16deeef6e4503cb4bc","text":"Reserve","correct":false},{"id":"3349300356cb3141ea939dcbdf749789","text":"Partition","correct":true},{"id":"180bc3b1c5619aaef40e803f49921012","text":"Spread","correct":false}]},{"id":"e64254c2-1a50-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"According to the AWS Shared Responsibility Model, which of the following is the customer responsible for?","explanation":"AWS is responsible for protecting the infrastructure that runs its services, which includes Amazon VPC. By comparison, the customer is responsible for what goes in the AWS Cloud. This includes subnets (each of which consist of a range of IP addresses), security groups (each of which acts as a virtual firewall to control inbound and outbound traffic), and network ACLs as additional layers of security.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"97fd1873341a4d886cd8a23614cef0ff","text":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (VPC) Service","correct":false},{"id":"9175bb34d0aede26315b313b9432bcbb","text":"Security groups","correct":true},{"id":"3ca98dadd6a9bcbe75450331cd449df5","text":"Network access control lists (network ACLs)","correct":true},{"id":"74cd215a46d2bd96fc35dad7ef313283","text":"Subnets","correct":true}]},{"id":"332dccb8-1a46-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following CIDR block size ranges applies to IPv4 addresses in Amazon VPC?","explanation":"For IPv4 addresses, the VPC CIDR block size can be anywhere from /16 to /28.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/vpc-ip-addressing.html","title":"IP Addressing in Your VPC"}],"answers":[{"id":"b23abf46c1e7e117251291617bac5c56","text":"/8 to /36","correct":false},{"id":"d312bf1a99a33142c6a946375494aa20","text":"/12 to /32","correct":false},{"id":"699292f46538d2bf62bace8334097bb6","text":"1/ to /40","correct":false},{"id":"30575066a7baaedf5c35a22bc44a6964","text":"/16 to /28","correct":true}]},{"id":"2cae08d8-1bce-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following types of data transfer concerning Amazon EC2 are free?","explanation":"All data transfer in to EC2 instances from the Internet is free. So is data transfer out of EC2 to CloudFront. Data transfer pricing out from EC2 to the Internet is free as long as it does not exceed 1 GB per month. Since this condition is not included in Response B, it isn’t correct.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/on-demand/#Data_Transfer","title":"EC2 Instance Pricing – Data Transfer"}],"answers":[{"id":"9a1bfe89c1c91cf60b45ef77bf406e09","text":"Data transfer out from EC2 to Amazon CloudFront","correct":true},{"id":"3b4e686ed0886b7be7e142139c38eb68","text":"Data transfer out from EC2 to the Internet","correct":false},{"id":"2f08e8cef2078b8c6479a4b91faeeec3","text":"Data transfer in to EC2 from the Internet","correct":true},{"id":"279a4b71d3edd9b515bb71952e1a12c7","text":"Data transfer out from EC2 to AWS GovCloud","correct":false}]},{"id":"smnrxkfv-dk56-snvh-i93e-or0vfomvccbz","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are characteristics of cloud computing?","explanation":"The on-demand delivery via the internet of services with pay-as-you-go pricing characterizes cloud computing. Services incurred from a cloud services provider are operating expenses, not capital expenses. Capital Expenditure (CAPEX) is less common with the cloud, in favour of Operational Expenditure (OPEX). Skills and training for personnel are required to leverage Cloud Computing","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"dcfe379beaf88dbe9d59e7fcecf6f98a","text":"Services are delivered via the Internet.","correct":true},{"id":"2b34d3fef0b313e0047a2557d9842378","text":"Pay-as-you-go pricing","correct":true},{"id":"ebc744edbd870e96fe9e680b407ad053","text":"On-demand delivery","correct":true},{"id":"481f1c72f1007c1ac8e4a484b47af4f2","text":"Cloud charges are Capital Expenditures.","correct":false},{"id":"9b670633c5238ca5a17dd651c3a63662","text":"No extra skills or training are required.","correct":false}]},{"id":"cd73d505-c09a-44cb-a7fa-0ac6be0f5c99","domain":"tech","question":"Upon attempting to create an additional S3 bucket, you realize that you have reached your S3 bucket limit in your AWS account. You anticipate creating even more S3 buckets in the future for your photos and documents. Which of the following is the quickest solution?","explanation":"The key word here is 'quickest'. Granted, you can delete the S3 buckets of your choice, and you can try consolidating files into select buckets and deleting the emptied ones. But that could be quite a hassle to do, compared to simply requesting a service limit increase at the AWS Support Center. By default, you can create up to 100 buckets in an AWS account, and that is a limit that AWS does not override without officially requesting for a service limit increase.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/BucketRestrictions.html","title":"Bucket Restrictions and Limitations"}],"answers":[{"id":"104e2902668d313ccfbc1bc78457e84d","text":"Delete the S3 buckets that you barely use.","correct":false},{"id":"e7b93b6f7bea9c58f27912c7974c74d4","text":"Submit a service limit increase.","correct":true},{"id":"340d5ba6fcedb315c6adee97b1239f3f","text":"Consolidate files into half of the S3 buckets and delete the empty ones.","correct":false},{"id":"46bca3e00e40780aa04c28899f5bbe6b","text":"Simply create the S3 bucket; AWS will automatically override the bucket limit.","correct":false}]},{"id":"43e53065-cb82-4d76-a75d-8407d8f0d339","domain":"tech","question":"What two things make up a tag?","explanation":"Each tag consists of a key and a value. For each resource, each tag key must be unique, and each tag key can have only one value.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/cost-alloc-tags.html","title":"AWS Tags"}],"answers":[{"id":"689202409e48743b914713f96d93947c","text":"Value","correct":true},{"id":"b5e6800855208fbd66985d5f570ffd70","text":"Encryption String","correct":false},{"id":"22c56699c70b96c6c2351fbf86177472","text":"Primary key value","correct":false},{"id":"897356954c2cd3d41b221e3f24f99bba","text":"Key","correct":true}]},{"id":"2srflb2w-gpba-wyok-a3ts-v64r4v1vd57h","domain":"tech","question":"You use containers to host your microservices, and you need to route traffic to those applications using a single load balancer. Which of the following services should you use to accomplish this?","explanation":"This routing can be done only with an Application Load Balancer.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticloadbalancing/details/#details","title":"About the ALB"}],"answers":[{"id":"37e242ab2d525505933bbdb47d50d2b9","text":"Route53","correct":false},{"id":"7be6a0f173a965818e92c1df46c6626e","text":"AWS CodeDeploy","correct":false},{"id":"b3b5475001f327d331389c6f07ff7c3a","text":"Application Load Balancer","correct":true},{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":false}]},{"id":"ltl6jev0-2f05-xevd-rnut-yi3l7ar7nzk1","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are principles of sound design when it comes to reliability?","explanation":"The elasticity of cloud computing means that you never need to over-provision or manage change at the resource level.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"2c081b2e4ef662d134361511c0f138e1","text":"Manage change at the individual resource level.","correct":false},{"id":"c57c5e34d89769a30ca48ef1c1155033","text":"Scale horizontally.","correct":true},{"id":"7f20528f07a394778f02e20e5453fc02","text":"When in doubt, over-provision.","correct":false},{"id":"25ddbfce9d53b8f5a9e09aad85948b96","text":"Stop guessing about your capacity requirements.","correct":true}]},{"id":"7b242f9e-5541-40b9-94c3-ff760252f026","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following scenarios are examples of scaling an IT architecture vertically?","explanation":"To scale vertically is to increase the specifications of a single AWS resource as needed. For example, resizing EC2 or RDS instances for more CPU, memory, or network capabilities is scaling vertically. Adding more EC2 or RDS instances, on the other hand, is scaling horizontally because it involves the increase in the number of resources, rather than the increase in each resource’s capabilities.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"f9de222cea376a61a621e215c4daf0dc","text":"Resizing an RDS instance type from db.r5.large to db.r5.2xlarge","correct":true},{"id":"67c96e88044c732523807882de714af3","text":"Adding two more RDS instances","correct":false},{"id":"d2ed8876ad5d876850ebcde76e28bd9f","text":"Adding two more EC2 instances","correct":false},{"id":"4fd553484e87f00281d8e2d07df1c3ac","text":"Resizing an EC2 instance type from a1.medium to a1.xlarge for more CPU and memory power","correct":true}]},{"id":"bce6da84-1c95-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Upon which of these measurements is AWS Lambda pricing based?","explanation":"With AWS Lambda, you are charged based on the number of requests for your functions and the amount of time (duration) it takes for your code to execute.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lambda/pricing/","title":"AWS Lambda Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"a817cbcc67f9a1988581b7d71d401622","text":"Number of requests","correct":true},{"id":"880a586b8b9c63efeba6c7f9afae7dc0","text":"Data transfer","correct":false},{"id":"e02d2ae03de9d493df2b6b2d2813d302","text":"Duration","correct":true},{"id":"4789f23283b3a61f858b641a1bef19a3","text":"Memory","correct":false}]},{"id":"aaa7dqnz-f7nv-g9bl-zfw2-2xko23ptcj2t","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for managing when storing data in S3?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model for managed services, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance). When it comes to S3, the customer is responsible for all aspects of the data being stored on S3, and who has access to manage the S3 service for that account","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"6c507c7b28d852214aa62ba95c5c7009","text":"Who has access to data you stored on the S3 Service","correct":true},{"id":"ae48532652716e286fa0be350d5545e3","text":"Who has access to the storage hardware","correct":false},{"id":"3278fa01d394d47605876669eaea2957","text":"Who has access to the network hardware","correct":false},{"id":"f661780dbe84a95f44f8622698e4b2a9","text":"Who has access to the S3 Infrastructure Software","correct":false},{"id":"2f6823eab5248af1500c3b8329fab352","text":"Who has access to the S3 Service","correct":true}]},{"id":"c3f7fb72-1aba-4b4a-a88d-ab28709130ae","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following services are available 24x7 for all AWS Support Plans?","explanation":"All AWS Support plans provide 24x7 access to customer service, documentation, and support forums. For 24x7 access to Cloud Support Engineers, you will specifically need to get a Business or Enterprise Support plan.","links":[{"url":"https://console.aws.amazon.com/support/plans/home?#/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"a42a69de8cb0bc12c105962bb2df8561","text":"Support forums","correct":true},{"id":"df710f89ebb9e663bd3d66607a0bf413","text":"AWS documentation","correct":true},{"id":"ba4ffb983499bcebaa93c87030f33728","text":"Cloud Support Engineers","correct":false},{"id":"2273d1167a6212812d95dc8fadbae78e","text":"Customer service","correct":true}]},{"id":"80c462fa-2fa6-11ea-aec2-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS Support plans provide access to online self-paced labs for training staff?","explanation":"Only the Enterprise support plan provides access to online self-paced labs.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false}]},{"id":"5fd1imv7-lqes-7e9n-vz33-eau71532v2ly","domain":"security","question":"How does AWS Shield Standard help protect your environment?","explanation":"AWS Shield Standard is included at no extra cost but will only block DDOS attacks on your AWS resources - it will not scan the contents of incoming or outgoing traffic (this is a function of WAF) and will not protect your environment from viruses","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/waf/latest/developerguide/shield-chapter.html","title":"AWS Shield"}],"answers":[{"id":"55063c26653acc06bd00cc13e1acc3a4","text":"By scanning your instances for viruses","correct":false},{"id":"3e6fc5c29a49e9d5c54bd4950ad5cbe0","text":"By scanning outgoing application traffic for sensitive information","correct":false},{"id":"84009024e233c4995b00c514474f0ae5","text":"By Blocking DDOS attacks","correct":true},{"id":"b1d6309ddb9cc2f856af5a3bab83f37e","text":"By scanning incoming application traffic for know attacks","correct":false}]},{"id":"35f041db-16e3-4bb3-825d-7ab528bddd1b","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following falls under AWS compute services category?","explanation":"EC2, Lightsail, and Elastic Beanstalk fall under the compute umbrella of AWS services. EFS and AWS Backup are classified as storage services, and Amazon RDS is classified as database services.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/","title":"Amazon Web Services (AWS)"}],"answers":[{"id":"9e10649cd5a6507c47e44a66dc03eb5b","text":"Amazon Lightsail","correct":true},{"id":"ce1a41ee0352cee512475ef6a6233963","text":"Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2)","correct":true},{"id":"d2a6652ddeb631da029d1f2806e11fdc","text":"Amazon Elastic File System (EFS)","correct":false},{"id":"ce52d2cff6e50f2e74505e0c70d072b3","text":"AWS Backup","correct":false},{"id":"98492fcf8e38ae7ea331e271498d5275","text":"Amazon Relational Database Services (RDS)","correct":false},{"id":"765c63bdfc41e7ae2614191faa2b0d0a","text":"Amazon Elastic Beanstalk","correct":true}]},{"id":"fxef69cs-hn8k-lhl3-tlj6-g8e4sf2o4lud","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following are programmatic access types enabling users to interact with AWS services?","explanation":"The CLI, the API, and the SDK are programmatic access types enabling users to interact with AWS services, as long as they are authorized to do so. PHP is a seperate programming language.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/APIReference/Welcome.html","title":"Programmatic Access to AWS"}],"answers":[{"id":"2fec392304a5c23ac138da22847f9b7c","text":"PHP","correct":false},{"id":"91af5705f16502125e8b2187e64202c0","text":"CLI","correct":true},{"id":"f20e3c5e54c0ab3d375d660b3f896f6a","text":"SDK","correct":true},{"id":"db974238714ca8de634a7ce1d083a14f","text":"API","correct":true}]},{"id":"bd8ac490-21fe-451e-a3e6-6dfa221fb389","domain":"concepts","question":"Deploying your EC2 instances across multiple AZs will help address which Cloud Concept?","explanation":"Having resources across multiple AZ is one way to design for High Availability - the concept that your services in cloud should be designed to tolerate failures in the underlying cloud infrastructure. AWS allows you to do this by providing Availability Zones - each one is independent from the others, and a failure in one should not impact the others. Therefore, if you deploy your application in 2 instances in 2 AZs, and one of the AZs fails, you will still have 1 instance running your application. Automation relates simplifying common repeated tasks and removing the human element. Although scaleability and elasticity (the ability to increase resources according to needs and the ability to go up and down in resources as needed) look like they might fit, as we are talking specifically about Multiple AZs in the question High Availability is the more correct answer","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":true},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false}]},{"id":"ef32cbf3-49b8-406a-aa2d-eaff05300839","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the below is correct when looking at Regions, Availability Zones, Edge Location and Datacentres?","explanation":"Edge locations are a part of AWS' content distribution network, and are separate from Regions and AZs. The number of Edge Locations around the world is greater than that of Regions and Availability Zones, in order to reduce latency between your content and your customers - the more that exist, the greater the chance there is one where you need it.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/?p=ngi&loc=2","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"9fe244cde3895fdb2a60650e6154c15b","text":"The number of Availability Zones is the same as the number of Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"78f3c24434277d629cc0a0d14f18c598","text":"There are more Edge locations than Availability zones","correct":true},{"id":"5810cb8fea9cc8e7773f9cc96fdd6c51","text":"There are more Regions than Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"b8ecf41dfa2a8f2d576a9407c87dadf5","text":"There are more Availability Zones then Edge Locations","correct":false}]},{"id":"g7u8frqb-st05-cduw-gbms-boj1g5a4xb99","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below best describes DynamoDB?","explanation":"DynamoDB is a fast and flexible NoSQL database. NoSQL databases are non-relational, and have a dynamic structure, whereas SQL is relational and has a pre-defined structure. MySQL is a type of SQL database and Mongo is a type of NoSQL database, but neither of these are DynamoDB. ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/dynamodb/","title":"DynamoDB"}],"answers":[{"id":"bbd2da8aa588d6741d84847621ad4503","text":"DynamoDB is a Mongo database","correct":false},{"id":"f311f0c1ec783313330a4fd83fbb6200","text":"DynamoDB is a NoSQL database","correct":true},{"id":"482666cddcef688e890d4b901ebf8a32","text":"DynamoDB is a MySQL database","correct":false},{"id":"30baf17e85e225ed9bb718ded752d263","text":"DynamoDB is a an SQL database","correct":false}]},{"id":"11337c6a-2fe1-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following statements is true of Amazon Aurora?","explanation":"The only statement that is not true is Response A. Aurora is compatible with MySQL and PostgresSQL, but not with MariaDB.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonRDS/latest/AuroraUserGuide/CHAP_AuroraOverview.html","title":"What is Amazon Aurora?"}],"answers":[{"id":"df120e572996d59e2f2d7eb17eea6c1a","text":"It is compatible with MariaDB.","correct":false},{"id":"2b4cdcd7f9dc266e76ab58a968be68b5","text":"It can deliver up to five times the throughput of MySQL.","correct":true},{"id":"e17ce0919bb302cc40193f3b80181176","text":"It can auto-scale up to 64 TB of storage space.","correct":true},{"id":"02a6a3634e2fbdb506decbb529496d8a","text":"It is a Relational Database Service (RDS) database engine developed by Amazon.","correct":true}]},{"id":"yvxo9l3i-wh4o-2dqm-3mnu-snzqe8qbcn6w","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes an AWS Region?","explanation":"A Region is a distinct location within a geographic area designed to provide high availability to a specific geography. Regions are a key concept in AWS' Global Infrastructure - each is made up of one or more isolated (within that region) Availability Zones. There are often multiple AWS Regions on each continent, such as North America","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"8c91beabafc69d771d60455febdc0927","text":"A console that gives you a quick, global picture of your cloud computing environment.","correct":false},{"id":"02994d9c387a384eeaa6efd09a6dd102","text":"A distinct location within a geographic area designed to provide high availability to a specific geography.","correct":true},{"id":"cd212d0c12772fef24104f0585e29933","text":"A collection of data centres that are spread evenly around a specific continent.","correct":false},{"id":"1230f90d0fb76db29194467e14f8e099","text":"A collection of databases that can only be accessed from a specific geographic region.","correct":false}]},{"id":"g817t8h6-2yd3-mhf7-wf2v-n82br09qszt7","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following Compliance certifications attests to the security of the AWS platform regarding credit card transactions?","explanation":"PCI DSS is a compliance program which must be followed by any organizations handling Credit Card data. AWS has achieved a PCI Level 1 certification, the highest level available","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/pci-data-privacy-protection-hipaa-soc-fedramp-faqs/","title":"AWS Compliance"}],"answers":[{"id":"74073bf9c7bfe155fe513fd4624ae2f2","text":"PCI DSS Level 1","correct":true},{"id":"7829c763646fba446ea5831ef095f756","text":"ISO 27001","correct":false},{"id":"7aa6bd3f5ca63135c1f75edd80d7a6ba","text":"SOC 2","correct":false},{"id":"faf72a9a0f8e7e240ee1346d6e2056e3","text":"SOC 1","correct":false}]},{"id":"5d3e351c-1f62-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following constitute Multi-Factor Authentication for signing into the AWS Management Console?","explanation":"Multi-factor authentication, or MFA, adds an extra layer of protection to your user name and password when logging in to the AWS Management Console. To sign in, you would need two factors, which are 1.) the user name and password; and 2.) an authentication code from an AWS-supported MFA software app.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/features/mfa/","title":"IAM - Multi-factor Authentication"}],"answers":[{"id":"59f2c8e6be7c2804d73e2f0bad9b26e8","text":"User name, password, and authentication code","correct":true},{"id":"f3499a9f28ab4d9412f8dc5e818c8ccd","text":"User name and password","correct":false},{"id":"4cf20b6f419df88d662bb7d18bd7c7e1","text":"Password and authentication code","correct":false},{"id":"36562a3012cb05bd90eed776b4760dc7","text":"User name and authentication code","correct":false}]},{"id":"32af5742-3072-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is the AWS email and calendaring service?","explanation":"With WorkMail, you can send and receive email and manage your calendars in the AWS cloud. By contrast, WorkSpaces is for providing a cloud-based desktop user experience, WorkDocs is an enterprise-level storage and sharing service for improving employee productivity, and WorkLink is for providing secure mobile access to internal websites and mobile apps.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/","title":"AWS Documentation"},{"url":" https://docs.aws.amazon.com/workmail/latest/userguide/what_is.html","title":"What Is Amazon WorkMail?"}],"answers":[{"id":"8cc40e114507046a03537b13d0f8fba9","text":"WorkSpaces","correct":false},{"id":"f5b309167cc0add83c6bca843f188e84","text":"WorkDocs","correct":false},{"id":"88b7abaa08028028e9a0f42dd6edc895","text":"WorkLink","correct":false},{"id":"3dee8a3d0ac81b151d8a0fa87c673799","text":"WorkMail","correct":true}]},{"id":"o8aqfsp4-kk6k-gyj7-frq7-4bpn7iv5zqm8","domain":"concepts","question":"You have a mission-critical application which must be globally available at all times. Which deployment strategy should you follow?","explanation":"A Multi-Region deployment will best ensure global availability. While it can be the most expensive, and complex to configure, Multi-Regional architectures will ensure that even if all Availability Zones in a single region fail due to a catastrophic event, your data will remain accessible.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"91d7ff212b9bda483701aeb4209ae5ec","text":"Deploy to all Availability Zones in your home region.","correct":false},{"id":"ec206762c0bea997a5b0f91783cce54f","text":"Multi-Availability Zone","correct":false},{"id":"86b2c5243e03e210528f020bad4efdb9","text":"Multi-VPC in two AWS Regions","correct":false},{"id":"e4ec2833a31f482abfdb31691f0351dc","text":"Multi-Region","correct":true}]},{"id":"2df4774c-2e69-4156-96c5-b1efbfba754f","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the below is correct when looking at Regions, Availability Zones, Edge Location and Datacentres?","explanation":"Regions contain two or more Availability Zones, which are themselves made up of one or more Datacentres. This means there will always be more AZs than Regions. Edge locations are separate from AZs and Regions, and there are more Edge Locations than Regions and Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/regions_az/?p=ngi&loc=2","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"26c658a3c4aee0122f0178a65f0ea80b","text":"There are more Availability Zones then Regions","correct":true},{"id":"29030db1d3f86fea8d8779a9c964c207","text":"There are more Availability Zones than Edge locations","correct":false},{"id":"f4b49cc5b3d286cd78cac99f03cecce3","text":"There are more Regions than Availability zones","correct":false},{"id":"f35fa3c5e765907efd6efa66bc1741c3","text":"The number of Availability Zones is the same as the number of Regions","correct":false}]},{"id":"rc4dwp79-ix5s-h912-sdcj-9gmmhl6zacte","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following is AWS' managed DDoS protection service?","explanation":"AWS Shield is AWS' managed DDoS protection service at Layer 4. AWS WAF provides protection from common exploits against your web applications at Layer 7, and does not protect against DDoS attacks.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/shield/?nc2=h_l3_dm","title":"About AWS Shield"}],"answers":[{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false},{"id":"303a25c2935ec1fdb01208b6f4f65688","text":"Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":true}]},{"id":"c127gqer-wn02-ljaa-xx5a-jpsogr3yw2ij","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS services are free to use?","explanation":"Whilst all of these services are free to use, the things they create or interact with can incur charges. For instance, a CloudFormation template is free to run, but if it creates an EC2 instance, you will be paying for that EC2 instance. Whilst some of the other services do have free tier entitlements or features, as a service, they do have general costs associated with them","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/pricing/services/","title":"AWS Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"37e242ab2d525505933bbdb47d50d2b9","text":"Route53","correct":false},{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":false},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"d85c80578ad0849a611c1056b63e385c","text":"VPC","correct":true},{"id":"248c1b0bcb74394beb4a08030c4a6847","text":"EBS","correct":false},{"id":"3d6cbd7db2a4fa389808ea6f4a5fc1bc","text":"Elastic Beanstalk","correct":true},{"id":"0f41d6f36f8eaee87ea08d9f4b1159e2","text":"RDS","correct":false},{"id":"caa58cad8d490fcdf1da0862623481fc","text":"Auto-Scaling","correct":true},{"id":"41dff7155cc7aeb11c06434f6a450bb3","text":"IAM","correct":true},{"id":"58e3bfbabf904de43a6a22aca509b0d8","text":"CloudFormation","correct":true}]},{"id":"rv438cbg-ow9h-jrfd-gxxt-a83ko2ojlo7c","domain":"concepts","question":"In AWS' Global Infrastructure, what are Edge Locations responsible for?","explanation":"Edge Locations host a Content Delivery Network called CloudFront.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"3d5bde6fd721f0872d6ad91a83e073cd","text":"Providing independent power grids to Availability Zones","correct":false},{"id":"e2dd2357c3f760b6df8cd9ef82402a0e","text":"Providing disaster recovery services","correct":false},{"id":"7e293752730d983b3fb263bc37525a5c","text":"Hosting a Content Delivery Network called CloudFront","correct":true},{"id":"0df5575df91cfdc3471135f97cd57b5b","text":"Providing redundant backup to your AWS services","correct":false}]},{"id":"f073f45a-0541-43a5-a1ae-4c67afb87086","domain":"security","question":"As an AWS customer, what is the best thing to do if you want to get periodic official statements to be notified of security and privacy events with AWS services?","explanation":"You will not get official security statements from the AWS News Blog, which provides current events regarding AWS. And while you can always send an email to request security announcements, chances are you will be redirected to the Security Bulletins page, where you can subscribe to an RSS feed to be updated on security and privacy issues.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/security/security-bulletins/?card-body.sort-by=item.additionalFields.bulletinDateSort&card-body.sort-order=desc","title":"Security Bulletins"}],"answers":[{"id":"520267b96af385f180fa3fd9ec26dc51","text":"Subscribe to the AWS News Blog.","correct":false},{"id":"ddd4a6bf26b1483b9221e364d190454f","text":"Email AWS directly to express your interest in receiving security announcements.","correct":false},{"id":"335ec04e733ed7b0bacd46bf6948b866","text":"Subscribe to the AWS Security Bulletin RSS feed.","correct":true},{"id":"ab09f1b93a71ea2e9b2634438d8c954a","text":"Email AWS Security to express your interest in receiving security announcements.","correct":false}]},{"id":"8af9065f-42ab-4684-937d-6ff9a21fce3a","domain":"tech","question":"You visit a clients site and get called into a corridor discussion. You are asked to describe the new (2019) URL structure for objects in S3.  Which of these do you use as a description.","explanation":"AWS has updated the URL format for objects in S3 in order to partition the name space.  This will introduce more consistency, but be aware that there are still multiple variation depending on feature and location.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-s3-path-deprecation-plan-the-rest-of-the-story/","title":"New S3 path format"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/general/latest/gr/rande.html#s3_region","title":"S3 Regional Endpoints"}],"answers":[{"id":"9b571c57c4bcb1635a0422505e741908","text":" https, then the bucket name, then dot, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then slash, then the object name","correct":true},{"id":"ae3cbeae173c8a519b7847f15141def6","text":" https, then the bucket name, then slash, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then slash, then the object name","correct":false},{"id":"db8e7027e46c062db1befedc330f0884","text":" https, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then dot, then the bucket name, then slash, then the object name","correct":false},{"id":"e9fd54ece61badbfe41eb84932fcb635","text":" http, then the object name, then dot, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then dot, then bucket the name","correct":false},{"id":"ab8096a72368e95dc6011f1758564494","text":" https, then the object name, then slash, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then slash, then bucket the name","correct":false},{"id":"a91ee87d632a84e3d44d1f44d80dc38e","text":" https, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then slash, then the bucket name, then slash, then the object name","correct":false},{"id":"f2a5230ac12d8264aebebe8dfedd74a5","text":" http, then the bucket name, then dot, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then slash, then the object name","correct":false}]},{"id":"ca0mnlws-zcum-4ktx-vhea-4j7tzi5qof7m","domain":"security","question":"What is the recommended way to give your applications running in EC2 permission to other AWS resources?","explanation":"You should use IAM Roles wherever possible to enable applications running on EC2 instances to access other AWS resources. This is the most secure method to do so. It is not possible to assign an IAM Group or User to an instance, and although using the Root Keys in you application would work this is HIGHLY insecure and should never be done, as the Root Keys have access to absolutely everything in your account.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/iam-roles-for-amazon-ec2.html","title":"IAM Roles for Amazon EC2"}],"answers":[{"id":"6bd8f4a2aff7022a330dc33c097a2f5a","text":"Create an IAM Role with appropriate permissions and assign it to the instance.","correct":true},{"id":"d12b50f23d2457b811312e994c2569d0","text":"Create an IAM User with appropriate permissions and assign it to the instance.","correct":false},{"id":"0bce771e576c7cf6bd90b9463d344860","text":"Create an IAM Group with appropriate permissions and assign it to the instance.","correct":false},{"id":"01943125f389f038045d6c0c56cafcce","text":"Create an Root Access Key and use it in the application.","correct":false}]},{"id":"e915ef52-2be6-4fba-8d62-b668f639c29a","domain":"billing","question":"To stay within the AWS Free Tier using Amazon EC2 for the first 12 months of having an AWS account, which of the following instance types should you use?","explanation":"One of the EC2 requirements for staying within the AWS Free Tier is using EC2 micro instances only. While the other instance types can be cheap, only t2.micro is eligibile for free tier usage","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/free/?all-free-tier.sort-by=item.additionalFields.SortRank&all-free-tier.sort-order=asc","title":"AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"1d4f2c610dbeb44e7ba09fed19564c76","text":"t2.micro","correct":true},{"id":"ab61127647912c159c3fc08e9a102efc","text":"t2.small","correct":false},{"id":"05c25e549fbb3f158f12a9945bff38ee","text":"t3.medium","correct":false},{"id":"cc114cafeb511c9cbe6666312f54a8de","text":"m5.medium","correct":false}]},{"id":"82395a22-1850-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are benefits of Amazon RDS read replicas?","explanation":"Amazon read replicas are copies of your source database instance and enhance performance by reducing the instance’s workload and increase availability when the instance fails. In addition, read replicas are designed for security because RDS sets up communication between them and the source DB instance using public key encryption. Automated backups are a feature of multi-AZ deployments, not a benefit of read replicas.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/details/read-replicas/","title":"Amazon RDS Read Replicas"}],"answers":[{"id":"9a444c669290fc78c2a35ebd7978f501","text":"Enhanced performance","correct":true},{"id":"ef9fb3f2791771e8bae6858776183460","text":"Increased availability","correct":true},{"id":"04698c3c0a8125713f9aa8b52980533f","text":"Automated backups","correct":false},{"id":"acb398041387588e9008c86fa3065023","text":"Designed for security","correct":true}]},{"id":"yhwuezmk-vte7-c3ty-x612-wvd1qi3aw2us","domain":"tech","question":"You’ve been tasked with assessing your AWS infrastructure in terms of cost optimization. Which of the following AWS services would help with this task? ","explanation":"AWS Trusted Advisor is an online tool that provides you with real-time guidance to help you provision your resources following AWS best practices.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/trustedadvisor/","title":"AWS Trusted Advisor"}],"answers":[{"id":"113b1ad9ce6cdc3a37ad8475bc9bb2b2","text":"AWS Systems Manager","correct":false},{"id":"739749e0ec278613ef4f8e6861efc722","text":"Trusted Advisor","correct":true},{"id":"ee58e6973ab1b8a94d5434399ac85129","text":"Cloud Trail","correct":false},{"id":"bd02384ebb7e76c74ae044ad5cf295c1","text":" AWS Personal Health Dashboard","correct":false}]},{"id":"hgb6veam-i287-99i8-3v3f-0sxjtcea43qf","domain":"tech","question":"How does S3 Transfer Acceleration help you get your data into S3 quicker?","explanation":"S3 Transfer Acceleration uses AWS' network of Edge Locations to ingest data, and then uses the most optimal path within its own network to reach S3. Although compression and splitting data up before upload can also help speed things up, these are not offered by transfer acceleration. AWS does not let you send in data on your own disks, and although Snowball does let you to send data in without going across the internet, it is only useful when working with massive amounts of data.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/transfer-acceleration.html","title":"Amazon S3 Transfer Acceleration"}],"answers":[{"id":"bded189801290994bc7203f5c28e9812","text":"By using AWS's network of Edge Locations to upload to a location closest to you before taking the most optimal path within AWS's network","correct":true},{"id":"9e82d26d8d807aff3537debfbdbbfa3f","text":"By splitting up your data into smaller chunks and uploading it simultaneously, then putting it back together on S3","correct":false},{"id":"25e2178eda752fbf1b65aca4d8e31d7e","text":"By letting you send the data in on a disk your provide (saving on upload times) then copying it to S3","correct":false},{"id":"7152ecba5a6dedddfb04c7c1751a7fc1","text":"By compressing your data to make it smaller for upload, then de-compressing it onto S3","correct":false}]},{"id":"8ae68d9e-7bf8-41c2-996a-a01fb1bf966a","domain":"billing","question":"Which tool can help you to compare the cost of hosting resources in AWS vs the cost of hosting in a traditional data centre?","explanation":"The TCO calculators allow you to estimate the cost savings when using AWS and provide a detailed set of reports.  Pricing Calculator can be used to estimate potential AWS spend, and AWS Budgets & Billing Alarms can help keep spend under control by alerting you when you breach a threshold.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/tco-calculator/","title":"AWS TCO Calculator"}],"answers":[{"id":"e84e1dd83afcda636af8a6ae32a58cef","text":"AWS TCO Calculator","correct":true},{"id":"e32a801c8e0beab6abb9361e937365be","text":"AWS Budgets","correct":false},{"id":"6b6f2097ec6555c2e09b7ed23571b3c5","text":"AWS Billing Alarms","correct":false},{"id":"1a98a10ad310a9ed66414dd3acb48e72","text":"AWS Pricing Calculator","correct":false}]},{"id":"e3b24121-862f-4b1e-8f4e-18e6f3f9e1e8","domain":"concepts","question":"VMware Cloud on AWS allows companies to migrate and extend their on-premises VMware vSphere-based environments to AWS Cloud using Amazon EC2. Which of the following choices accurately classifies this deployment model?","explanation":"Hybrid deployments connect infrastructure and applications between cloud-based resources and existing resources that are not located in the cloud. VMware Cloud on AWS is an example of a hybrid deployment, since it involves the on-premises environments of VMware and the cloud-based services of AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/hybrid/","title":"Hybrid Cloud with AWS"}],"answers":[{"id":"fb1b6e23a3767d2a31ef7899e6dd3f1e","text":"Hybrid","correct":true},{"id":"0fca8d17afc46bb08bd2d70a26cdf886","text":"On-Premises","correct":false},{"id":"c8e2277ecfb1427838c488c217f99466","text":"Cloud","correct":false},{"id":"d6eb128e4c8971dc397f021585391999","text":"Shared Services","correct":false}]},{"id":"3ygeb7pi-gjw6-mzi9-0kq5-03x2sygemst0","domain":"tech","question":"What happens when an RDS Master database in a Multi-AZ deployment goes down?","explanation":"Amazon RDS automatically performs a failover in the event of Loss of availability in primary Availability Zone, Loss of network connectivity to primary, Compute unit failure on primary, or Storage failure on primary","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/details/multi-az/#Failover_conditions","title":"Amazon RDS Multi-AZ Failover"}],"answers":[{"id":"b650a48a49e9b851bc85cc3720ef42f4","text":"RDS automatically fails over to the standby, which is promoted to Master.","correct":true},{"id":"6e0895c1d81409b9b1ea4c57b6022eba","text":"The asynchronous replication of RDS Multi-AZ deployments means you will suffer some data loss.","correct":false},{"id":"6e8a400152e499f96063d91a9447d9c2","text":"You must copy the attached EBS volume to the standby.","correct":false},{"id":"84e57d062c135e5df249a3e13b35780b","text":"You must use the AWS console to promote the standby to Master.","correct":false}]},{"id":"cckhl0ep-pmhf-g8be-yplb-dzr17jgnk6mn","domain":"security","question":"Where is the best place to store your Root User Access Key so that your application can use it to make requests to AWS?","explanation":"It is not recommended to use Root User account or access keys for any reason as these grant full unrestricted access to the entire account. Recommended practice is to follow the concept of \"Least Privilege\" and create am IAM user or role with just enough access to do what is needed and nothing more, and use those keys as required","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/general/latest/gr/aws-access-keys-best-practices.html","title":"Best Practices for Managing AWS Access Keys"}],"answers":[{"id":"503d72b0254a8561511b71a95f8eb8a7","text":"It should be configured as a parameter and held in the Key Management Store (KMS)","correct":false},{"id":"73532a5c24d7b4c1df276690bbaedfff","text":"In the .aws file in you application","correct":false},{"id":"9feb4a526584eae16c38880b7813f48c","text":"It needs to be coded directly into your application","correct":false},{"id":"2330278fe444dd9a6196cb146c97de7e","text":"Nowhere - you should not use the Root User access keys for this","correct":true}]},{"id":"8ilibd7u-7ml9-492r-etu0-n4zubf409ykt","domain":"tech","question":"Amazon Lightsail is an example of which of the following?","explanation":"Lightsail is AWS' Platform-as-a-Service (PaaS) offering - this means that when using Lightsail you don't need to worry about all the components that are required to deliver the Instance such as storage, data, and instance size as AWS manages all that for you. Amazon Lightsail takes away many of the complexities of managing an Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS) solution, like some of the networking. This can also be a drawback, if you want to have a highly configurable service. Since Lightsail lets you run a variety of fully-features applications, it is neither a Software as a Service (SaaS), nor Function as a Service (FaaS) offering ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lightsail/","title":"About Lightsail"}],"answers":[{"id":"68c0c53c6a8ab47f4b611dbf1c347a26","text":"Software as a Service","correct":false},{"id":"0fdc9e547679a07630645143e79cce26","text":"Infrastructure as a Service","correct":false},{"id":"8f637a063500ec391f887ff70bda5f30","text":"Platform as a Service","correct":true},{"id":"f53d5c67ce1a2058f77a32af9a7d0c66","text":"Functions as a Service","correct":false}]},{"id":"f119625a-2f3b-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Your Project Manager needs to know the daily spend of the company’s AWS account over the last 60 days to consider creating and implementing cost-effective measures. What should you do?","explanation":"Cost Explorer provides a trio of preconfigured views designed to quickly get you to common spends in your AWS environment. For viewing the daily spend over the last 60 days, your Project Manager needs to click the 'Daily Spend View' link. AWS Budgets is for generating automatic alerts when your AWS costs or usage exceed, or are forecasted to exceed, the thresholds you set; it is not for tracking your spend.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/billing-what-is.html","title":"What Is AWS Billing and Cost Management?"}],"answers":[{"id":"ae4dff5b9f90f7f36261f1743d9c6eb1","text":"Direct him to Monthly Spend by Linked Account View in AWS Cost Explorer.","correct":false},{"id":"224e965acad73b5fc7fd31b503e947db","text":"Direct him to Daily Spend View in AWS Cost Explorer.","correct":true},{"id":"e3963c15d2d033b249d8f75f4b7c05ff","text":"Direct him to AWS Budgets.","correct":false},{"id":"3061bd4594121d528b00ebc0b3cabd8b","text":"Direct him to Monthly Spend by Service View in AWS Cost Explorer.","correct":false}]},{"id":"812wx3ht-7wy1-12kp-ow6n-k8a1y15t2w6v","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the below are common use cases for S3?","explanation":"Common use cases for Amazon S3 include storing application assets and static web hosting. AWS does not recommend using S3 for filesystems or for database storage.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/gsg/S3-gsg-CommonUseScenarios.html","title":"S3 Use Cases"}],"answers":[{"id":"28cbd7a2db3e5bd8ca1ba00ac2e966a8","text":"Storing application assets","correct":true},{"id":"f920ea13fb606314d3259470cdc8d429","text":"Installing a filesystem","correct":false},{"id":"484bf39587ca9f0fed0666ab7d34543a","text":"Hosting a relational database","correct":false},{"id":"181f55b567c0f81904aac0d8deeb5e17","text":"Static web hosting","correct":true}]},{"id":"ff53359b-3559-40fd-9210-608f87ed6a5f","domain":"security","question":"Broadly speaking as a customer of AWS you responsible for:","explanation":"Generally speaking, as a customer of AWS you responsible for the security IN the cloud - meaning that you are responsible for the data, consumption and in-account configuration of AWS services","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"2245b1bb4da8871fd09d4b5b6c52555e","text":"Security IN the cloud","correct":true},{"id":"597b531cfe7d260c96c8ec4c4d4365ba","text":"None of security - AWS will manage all security for you","correct":false},{"id":"e5a10169b294451720bbfc8cee548381","text":"Security both IN and OF the cloud","correct":false},{"id":"2ac2679f0084e375060c216fe7477ab4","text":"Security OF the cloud","correct":false}]},{"id":"0d572528-b848-4613-91c2-7010b8be3537","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services are Global by default?","explanation":"Of the above, IAM, Route53 and CloudFront are AWS services that by default are not region specific.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/autoscaling/","title":"AWS Auto Scaling"}],"answers":[{"id":"e95e5a2a3cc8625bca3d71b817367e2d","text":"Elastic Load Balancer","correct":false},{"id":"bef6cb89241de238f082cb243307ad1b","text":"CloudFront","correct":true},{"id":"41dff7155cc7aeb11c06434f6a450bb3","text":"IAM","correct":true},{"id":"37e242ab2d525505933bbdb47d50d2b9","text":"Route53","correct":true},{"id":"0f41d6f36f8eaee87ea08d9f4b1159e2","text":"RDS","correct":false}]},{"id":"0mdd9dnl-ji3o-hjum-lyr4-wtpoks65v0z9","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following statements about AWS Region is true?","explanation":"A region is a geographical area divided into Availability Zones. Each region contains at least two publicly accessible Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"bec481a5e2c63bfc93d4922d5845bd2b","text":"Regions are only available in some locations globally","correct":false},{"id":"1c52cae4b07ea355b6bf0d1522efc7e7","text":"Regions are made up of Availability Zones","correct":true},{"id":"fddc13d769887bc62fc14c8d844e1aa9","text":"Regions are generally specific geographical areas","correct":true},{"id":"2cf30d8c571fe080cdd53d0a78db5689","text":"Regions are automatically fully synchronized to contain the same data globally","correct":false}]},{"id":"89c58d68-554a-45ea-9da8-fcf90103d4e8","domain":"concepts","question":"The Chief Marketing Officer of the hotel chain you work for would like to implement voice recognition capabilities in rooms so customers can request services without picking up the phone. Competitors have already begun rolling out these technologies in an attempt to improve their customers’ experience. Which benefit of the AWS cloud would you most emphasize to the CMO in your business case for creating an AWS-based solution?","explanation":"The AWS cloud provides instant access to new technologies. Companies can move with agility to satisfy new business requirements and meet competitive demands. There is a very low barrier of entry for innovation. If a solution is not meeting expectations, services can be instantly de-provisioned. The other three options will also prove to be benefits of deploying in the AWS cloud, but the use case emphasizes the need to move quickly against competitive threats.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"6cdf2174e24cf3e60f016e85f00c34ff","text":"Deploy Globally in Minutes","correct":false},{"id":"ecbe6eb71bcb646d89d2e361dfa84c21","text":"Cost Savings","correct":false},{"id":"241bb470b0110efc8b5609f7311b0bb1","text":"Agility","correct":true},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false}]},{"id":"3edc2ffd-d684-4cf1-83f9-b782b6782711","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following pricing models are available for EC2?","explanation":"EC2 has four different pricing models, On Demand, Reserved, Spot and Dedicated Hosts. Each pricing model has been created for different workload types and use cases.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"244492cdce9dce0555c52ebe1182e0a3","text":"On Demand","correct":true},{"id":"a687560297f056cb18ffb527b46f79b4","text":"Dot Instances","correct":false},{"id":"942d4e37dd5607ab68e54755540d4a47","text":"Reserved","correct":true},{"id":"acbe4e201e8e2ac67830983f9c8d7970","text":"Dedicated Hosts","correct":true},{"id":"abf84cb49aaf1ec8157f80e4d27d011e","text":"Hybrid Instances","correct":false}]},{"id":"0e20ce8c-1a57-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following statements is true of AWS Regions?","explanation":"AWS Regions are geographical areas that consist of locations called Availability Zones. Because they are isolated from each other, there is no automatic replication of resources between them. In addition, data transfer between Regions is not free; there is a charge associated with that.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-regions-availability-zones.html","title":"Regions, Availability Zones, and Local Zones"}],"answers":[{"id":"f941bbe63c60384543e03468d67e8a94","text":"They are independent geographical areas.","correct":true},{"id":"96676b55f4ae2e27083b81e373c80e5a","text":"They automatically replicate resources among each other.","correct":false},{"id":"6f99c65ce03a0a9018c608fc49149883","text":"There are no charges for data transferred between them.","correct":false},{"id":"3a4116551c9039850c094ec59ecc726c","text":"They are composed of Availability Zones.","correct":true}]},{"id":"918c058b-8c3d-4858-aa1b-de986b3379af","domain":"security","question":"Which following statement is true of newly created security groups with their default rules?","explanation":"By default, new security groups start with only an outbound rule to allow all traffic to leave the instances. You must add rules to enable any inbound traffic.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/VPC_SecurityGroups.html","title":"Security Groups for Your VPC"}],"answers":[{"id":"d21ab4dffc222de4dfe6fddddca20b1f","text":"New security groups allow both incoming and outbound traffic.","correct":false},{"id":"66152806bd7636ccc1a33303917cdddd","text":"New security groups allow only outbound traffic and block all incoming traffic.","correct":true},{"id":"8fbe4c39dc7d852a0b8aaa5b889b1ff1","text":"New security groups block outbound traffic and allow all incoming traffic.","correct":false},{"id":"d00cd55aa36c87aedb13b4c0829aa462","text":"New security groups block both incoming and outbound traffic.","correct":false}]},{"id":"234bba0a-2156-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":" Which of the following falls under the AWS compute services category?","explanation":"Amazon Elastic Beanstalk, EKS, and Lambda are examples of AWS compute services. EMR and Elasticsearch Service are analytics tools.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/","title":"AWS Documentation"}],"answers":[{"id":"765c63bdfc41e7ae2614191faa2b0d0a","text":"Amazon Elastic Beanstalk","correct":true},{"id":"b32528fd7ed7465487910de3228929ab","text":"Amazon Elastic MapReduce (EMR)","correct":false},{"id":"480c9b5f979d1ce95ea2a58b09826d1b","text":"Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (EKS)","correct":true},{"id":"1dd30e8d60c2a200781dbcc9286f0919","text":"Elasticsearch Service","correct":false},{"id":"afe034817454f6fc529648e38cd32c26","text":"Amazon Lambda","correct":true}]},{"id":"7a194fa6-5966-4548-9b32-ac602a517ac8","domain":"concepts","question":"With AWS services, you can use as many resources as you need, as well as use them when you need them. Which of the following terms can be applied to this concept?","explanation":"Working in a traditional infrastructure environment means that you have to deal with fixed resources, which is comparatively costly and labor-intensive. By contrast, AWS services are much more convenient; the services provide the ability to use as many resources as you need and dispose of them when you no longer need them. That’s why such resources are both temporary and disposable.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for the Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"5936fc4450b6f3f75cc6fe08d2890b77","text":"Temporary resources","correct":true},{"id":"83ec702ebd8e13f87318dba136356773","text":"Dedicated resources","correct":false},{"id":"fd3ca13906a4c1e05f791d27dbc66914","text":"Disposable resources","correct":true},{"id":"e035a6f9ed7c8c3c99e48b95e32cc364","text":"Fixed resources","correct":false}]},{"id":"h0bz8vyv-zk25-7xf6-p1l3-v0qntk7m5yjw","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are types of cloud computing deployments?","explanation":"The three types of cloud deployments are: \r\n Public - where everyone and anyone can access that cloud's resources \r\n Private - also called on-premises where the underlying cloud infrastructure is owned and operated by a private entity for the sole use of that entity \r\n Hybrid - which is a mix of both. \r\n Mixed cloud is not a term used to describe a cloud computing deployment","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/types-of-cloud-computing/","title":"Types of Cloud Computing"}],"answers":[{"id":"761883c0d5c55fba5b200ac8ac0d86e5","text":"Public cloud","correct":true},{"id":"7d22e2d665f6d51244a33f26e96904f9","text":"Mixed cloud","correct":false},{"id":"cb38b39495aded16d3565297386a9c9e","text":"Private cloud","correct":true},{"id":"2dde6ce98c19e445f3c47a7a9d166f04","text":"Hybrid cloud","correct":true}]},{"id":"b7d5jc0p-zg8y-0hwp-3cjv-2yxp349xk58p","domain":"security","question":"You want to streamline access management for your AWS administrators by assigning them a pre-defined set of permissions based on their job role - which of the below is the best way to approach this?","explanation":"Using IAM Groups lets you create a list of pre-defined permissions that any user made a part of that group will be granted. Roles are primarily used to grant AWS resources permissions to other AWS resources and generally are not for end-users. Amazon Cognito is a service that help authenticate users to your apps, and not the AWS console itself.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_groups.html","title":"IAM Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"48fb6d39f4c7857dc342d789480a20ea","text":"Use AWS Organizations","correct":false},{"id":"71f7b94ac76ec4aa2860353bc1120591","text":"Use IAM Roles","correct":false},{"id":"ffc1a593680549bf1bc0e966a70f0683","text":"Use IAM Groups","correct":true},{"id":"28639700aadbc704e3daae5ba44ab388","text":"Use Amazon Cognito","correct":false}]},{"id":"sf55l98e-bpq0-sh7t-wkah-ex19vhdc9bie","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following support services do all accounts receive as part of the AWS Support Basic tier?","explanation":"The AWS Support Basic tier is the free support given to all AWS Accounts. All accounts receive Billing Support, because every customer needs an avenue to lodge disputes, or make requests around their billing. 24x7 Support, Architectural Support, and access to a Technical Account Manager are all elements of paid plans.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"c7703baf6849325c6dd9df112e8b4b85","text":"Billing Support","correct":true},{"id":"6ef823966f6d09ca49ae0117fbeb6f17","text":"Architectural Support","correct":false},{"id":"4e88de53dbfa7fddf03f15ad5fd53eec","text":"Technical Account Manager","correct":false},{"id":"30c247eb11a68c65f4625c0a83e97cdb","text":"24/7 support via phone and chat","correct":false}]},{"id":"ve84vsab-pgl4-m9ys-7xbu-495l9begz11r","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following compute services is ideal if you need to run a simple website or a simple e-commerce application?","explanation":"Lightsail is ideal for simple websites or simple e-commerce applications.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/lightsail/","title":"About Lightsail"}],"answers":[{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"04a7da3c5b04cad85da1eebb92315b8b","text":"Lambda","correct":false},{"id":"b21eea42e76007ac061cf37a5a41037d","text":"Lightsail","correct":true},{"id":"3d6cbd7db2a4fa389808ea6f4a5fc1bc","text":"Elastic Beanstalk","correct":false}]},{"id":"5l7vjhuv-wf9j-de1i-9aj4-e9dlg8u6cc76","domain":"billing","question":"Your Development team uses four on-demand EC2 instances, and your QA team has 5 reserved instances, only three of which are being used. Assuming all AWS accounts are under a single AWS Organization, how will the Development team's instances be billed?","explanation":"Assuming all instances are in the same AWS Organization, the reserved instance pricing for the unused QA instances will be applied to two of the four Dev instances.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/reserved-instances/pricing/","title":"EC2 Instance Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"b04b07a9c68b5b505f53afccb5616743","text":"The pricing for the reserved instances will shift from QA to Dev.","correct":false},{"id":"a6d19cc18b59af08baaa0f8247fca355","text":"The Dev team will be billed for two instances at on-demand prices and two instances at the reserved instance price.","correct":true},{"id":"ecadbc09799c3807dfed5bd9ee9c6159","text":"All the Dev team's instances will be billed at the on-demand rate.","correct":false},{"id":"3ea9a50157f205cce00d0db169117711","text":"All the Dev instances will be billed at the reserved instance rate.","correct":false}]},{"id":"pzjuwu91-24rb-x77o-tzlj-dzpn3pvo3v3v","domain":"security","question":"You need to use an AWS service to assess the security and compliance of your EC2 instances. Which of the following services should you use?","explanation":"AWS Inspector is an automated security assessment service that helps improve the security and compliance of applications deployed on AWS. AWS Trusted Advisor can give security recommendations about your AWS resources, but not within EC2 instances themselves. AWS Shield and WAF can protect EC2 instances, but don't possess any capabilities to assess their security and compliance","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/inspector/?nc2=h_m1","title":"About AWS Inspector"}],"answers":[{"id":"05f43441d2d29ae2bb38fc8596ca6ff7","text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","correct":false},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false},{"id":"7c90c8f2a24f3a1a28525f19fb2c75ab","text":"AWS Inspector","correct":true},{"id":"32685c9f0403b41381bf5f88788ad995","text":"AWS WAF","correct":false}]},{"id":"8dmul9q1-wi30-bo4k-81j9-ztcv7dgeoybt","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following EC2 instance types will realize a savings over time in exchange for a contracted term-of-service?","explanation":"EC2 Reserved Instances offer significant discounts for a contracted term-of-service, of up to 75% off. On-Demand instances are charged equally per-hour, regardless of how long they're run for. Spot instances are cheaper than On-Demand instances, but aren't intended for long term use","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"409aa157dda2d7faab6bf2938e322891","text":"Discount instances","correct":false},{"id":"bcc129e8d9496a05a331c903d4c5bcb0","text":"Reserved instances","correct":true},{"id":"991236e27b7cb98a2eeff8897b3e0bb4","text":"Spot instances","correct":false},{"id":"2a80e91907ea76d424690185914b6eae","text":"On-demand instances","correct":false}]},{"id":"cfea2363-9af8-4536-b812-8ea53c44b11b","domain":"security","question":"You just had a Data Analyst join the company, and you have been tasked with creating a new IAM user accordingly. Although the user has received all the necessary credentials, she realized that she cannot perform any Amazon RDS actions on the Clients table. Which of the following are possible solutions to this issue?","explanation":"By default, an IAM user can’t access anything in the AWS account. So, the inability to perform the RDS actions on the Clients table is not a technical or password issue. To grant the permission to do so, you would need to create an identity-based policy. However, if there is a group in the account with the permission policy that will grant such access, you can add the user to that group instead.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/introduction_access-management.html","title":"Overview of Access Management: Permissions and Policies"}],"answers":[{"id":"2f96bead1d7909e64836767c4e098acd","text":"Create an identity-based policy.","correct":true},{"id":"7731c1bfd28c89eee71012d973fa5407","text":"Double-check the credentials you sent to the user.","correct":false},{"id":"1971cb80efb016ad4254e3847a847434","text":"Supply the password necessary to log into the AWS console.","correct":false},{"id":"f46d75eb223838121ca6bec9ca08eaaa","text":"Create a ticket for the Help Desk to resolve the issue.","correct":false},{"id":"94412f8679d11dc0613f571ca4fba16b","text":"Add the user to the group that has the necessary permissions policy.","correct":true}]}]}}}}
